biogamergirl.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy - BioGamer Girl

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the [http://www.biogamergirl.com](http://www.biogamergirl.com/) and BioGamer Girl Magazine and governs data collections and usage, For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to BioGamer Girl Magazine include [http://www.biogamergirl.com](http://www.biogamergirl.com/), BioGamer Girl, BGG Media, BGG After Dark, [http://bggafterdark.biogamergirl.com](http://bggafterdark.biogamergirl.com/), BGG Productions, Travew and [http://travew.biogamergirl.com](http://travew.biogamergirl.com/). The BioGamer Girl website is an entertainment website/magazine that contains movies, TV shows, events, and video game news, reviews, features and interview site. By using the BioGamer Girl website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
BioGamer Girl may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase BioGamer Girl’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. BioGamer Girl may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by BioGamer Girl. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the services, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the BioGamer Girl website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through BioGamer Girl’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

BioGamer Girl encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from BioGamer Girl so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. BioGamer Girl is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the BioGamer Girl website.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
BioGamer Girl collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

BioGamer Girl may also use your personally identifiable information to inform your of other products or services available from BioGamer Girl and its affiliates. BioGamer Girl may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

BioGamer Girl does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

BioGamer Girl may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to BioGamer Girl, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.  
BioGamer Girl will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BioGamer Girl or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of BioGamer Girl; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BioGamer Girl, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**  
The BioGamer Girl website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned a specific page. For example, if you personalize BioGamer Girl pages, or register with BioGamer Girl site or services, a cookie helps BioGamer Girl to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same BioGamer Girl website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the BioGamer Girl features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the BioGamer Girl services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, BioGamer Girl uses the following: GeoTrust. When personal information (such as credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
BioGamer Girl does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Disconnecting your BioGamer Girl Account from Third Party Websites**  
You will be able to connect your BioGamer Girl account to third party account.  BY CONNECTING YOUR BIOGAMER GIRL ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCOURDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnet your account from a third party account at any time.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt -out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving  any or all communications from BioGamer Girl by contacting us here:  
**Webpage:** [http://www.biogamergirl.com](http://www.biogamergirl.com/)  
**Email:** biogamergirl@live.com  
**Phone:** (256) 273-9752

**Changes to this Statement**  
BioGamer Girl will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. BioGamer Girl encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how BioGamer Girl is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
BioGamer Girl welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that BioGamer Girl has not adhered to this Statement, please contact BioGamer Girl at:

BioGamer Girl Magazine (BGG Entertainment)  
P.O. Box 51  
Fyffe, Alabama 35971

**Email Address:**  
biogamergirl@live.com

**Telephone number:**  
(256) 273-9752

_Effective as of November 08, 2010_  
_*Updated October 09, 2012_
